const CARDS = [
    { front: "Сегодня", back: "Dzisiaj" },
    { front: "Пятница", back: "Piątek" },
    { front: "Утром", back: "Rano" },
    { front: "Февраль", back: "Luty" },
    { front: "Вчера", back: "Wczoraj" },
    { front: "Через час", back: "Za godzinę" },
    { front: "Суббота", back: "Sobota" },
    { front: "Скоро", back: "Wkrótce" },
    { front: "Октябрь", back: "Październik" },
    { front: "Каждый год", back: "Co roku" },
    { front: "Послезавтра", back: "Pojutrze" },
    { front: "На выходных", back: "W weekend" },
    { front: "Среда", back: "Środa" },
    { front: "Март", back: "Marzec" },
    { front: "Позавчера", back: "Przedwczoraj" },
    { front: "Август", back: "Sierpień" },
    { front: "Вечером", back: "Wieczorem" },
    { front: "Следующий месяц", back: "Przyszły miesiąc" },
    { front: "Через минуту", back: "Za minutę" },
    { front: "Декабрь", back: "Grudzień" },
    { front: "Следующий год", back: "Przyszły rok" },
    { front: "Воскресенье", back: "Niedziela" },
    { front: "Недавно", back: "Niedawno" },
    { front: "Этот год", back: "Ten rok" },
    { front: "Понедельник", back: "Poniedziałek" },
    { front: "Завтра", back: "Jutro" },
    { front: "Сентябрь", back: "Wrzesień" },
    { front: "Прошлый месяц", back: "Zeszły miesiąc" },
    { front: "Эта неделя", back: "Ten tydzień" },
    { front: "Январь", back: "Styczeń" },
    { front: "Днём", back: "W ciągu dnia" },
    { front: "Прошлый год", back: "Zeszły rok" },
    { front: "Апрель", back: "Kwiecień" },
    { front: "Вторник", back: "Wtorek" },
    { front: "Июль", back: "Lipiec" },
    { front: "Через два года", back: "Za dwa lata" },
    { front: "Каждый день", back: "Codziennie" },
    { front: "Четверг", back: "Czwartek" },
    { front: "Ночью", back: "W nocy" },
    { front: "Этот месяц", back: "Ten miesiąc" },
    { front: "Прошлая неделя", back: "Zeszły tydzień" },
    { front: "Май", back: "Maj" },
    { front: "Прошлый год", back: "Zeszły rok" },
    { front: "Июнь", back: "Czerwiec" },
    { front: "Позапрошлый год", back: "Dwa lata temu" },
    { front: "Следующая неделя", back: "Przyszły tydzień" },
    { front: "Ноябрь", back: "Listopad" },
    { front: "Через неделю", back: "Za tydzień" }
];
